Are you looking to learn what microservices are?
您是否想了解什么是微服务？
Or are you trying to get started and gain some real world hands on experience with.
或者，您正在尝试入门并获得一些实际操作经验。
Net microservices.
.Net微服务
If yes, then you are at the right course.
如果是，那么您就上对了课。
My name is Brogan and welcome to the course.
我叫布罗根，欢迎来到本课程。
Net Core Microservices.
.Net核心微服务
The Complete Guide.
完全指南
Microservices is one of the buzzword in programming.
微服务是编程领域的热门词汇之一。
If you look for a new job, microservices is one of the key features that is coming up more and more
如果你想找一份新工作，微服务是越来越多地出现的关键功能之一。
often.
经常。
Every time a system is lagging or it is getting too big, someone will have a suggestion that maybe
每当系统出现滞后或变得过于庞大时，就会有人提出建议，也许
we should look into microservices.
我们应该研究一下微服务。
But it is critical to understand what exactly it is and how to implement it correctly.
但关键是要了解它到底是什么，以及如何正确实施。
That is my motivation behind this course.
这就是我开设这门课程的动机。
My goal is to introduce you to the microservices architecture while giving you a real world project
我的目标是向你介绍微服务架构，同时为你提供一个真实世界的项目
to see how microservices communicate with each other and what are the problems that we encounter and
看看微服务之间是如何通信的，我们会遇到哪些问题，以及
how to solve them.
如何解决这些问题。
Microservices is made up of individual projects in simple terms, but in reality there is much more
简单地说，微服务是由单个项目组成的，但实际上还有更多内容
to microservices than that.
微服务
But as microservices are composed of individual APIs, we will be spending quite some time in building
但是，由于微服务是由单个应用程序接口组成的，我们将花费大量时间来构建
small APIs.
小型应用程序接口。
And then we will focus on the key concept of how individual API communicates with each other and how
然后，我们将重点讨论各个应用程序接口如何相互通信，以及如何
the microservices architecture comes together.
微服务架构
We will be building seven small API's in this course, including one API that will be responsible for
在本课程中，我们将构建七个小型应用程序接口，其中一个应用程序接口将负责
authentication and we will do that using Dotnet identity.
我们将使用 Dotnet 身份进行验证。
Once we build the APIs, then we will see how API communicates with each other.
一旦我们构建了应用程序接口，我们就会看到应用程序接口是如何相互通信的。
One of the most frustrating thing when you are learning something is when the course is outdated, because
在学习过程中，最令人沮丧的事情之一就是课程过时了，因为
of which I will always try to keep the content up to date.
我将始终努力更新其中的内容。
That way you will not be struggling with what is different in the new version.
这样你就不会纠结于新版本的不同之处。
If you are excited about what microservices are and you want to learn by building a real world project
如果你对微服务感到兴奋，并希望通过构建一个真实世界的项目来学习
in microservices, this is the course you are looking for.
这就是您要找的课程。
I hope you will join me in this exciting journey of microservices.
希望您能和我一起踏上这段激动人心的微服务之旅。
And let me show you what we will build in this course in the next video.
让我在下一个视频中向你展示我们将在本课程中构建的内容。